<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hainan Sanya Yazhou bay Sci-tech city news</title><link>https://yzbst.city/</link><description>Recent content on Hainan Sanya Yazhou bay Sci-tech city news</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://yzbst.city/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://yzbst.city/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yzbst.city/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://yzbst.city/about/hainan-yazhou-bay-science-and-technology-city-free-trade-port.jpeg"
width="9219"
height="3240"
srcset="https://yzbst.city/about/_hu1d1e58e1ab91ac8e3242cabb07bc6782_1066619_4be29aa7d04c730ba36ae7ee3775529d.jpeg 480w, https://yzbst.city/about/_hu1d1e58e1ab91ac8e3242cabb07bc6782_1066619_14318129ac751b554340f75a1a8c9438.jpeg 1024w"
loading="lazy"
alt="The view of Hainan free trade port, yazhou bay science and technoly city development is a key element in Hainan&amp;rsquo;s development"
class="gallery-image"
data-flex-grow="284"
data-flex-basis="682px"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Yazhou bay science and technology city (YZBSTC) is a key advanced technology park located on Hainan Island, China. The park contains incubators, accelerators, and enterprises working towards developing cutting-edge solutions in marine studies, deep-sea studies, agriculture, and biotechnology. Yazhou bay&amp;rsquo;s main focus is on seed breeding development and research in order to ensure a stable food supply in the future.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>According to the central government of China, the plan for the development of the Hainan FTP (free trade port) zone, the Yazhou Bay development area is set to be approximately 69.3sqm and focus on industries such as Nanfan seed breeding, deep-sea research, and scientific studies as well as IoT and advance agriculture.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Yazhou Bay science and technology city news (YZBSTC news) website (yzbst.city) is a non-government, privately held news and media site that enables a glance into the amazing city of Yazhou bay and the advanced technologies and developments it holds. The website will frequently cover news in YZBSTC, events, companies&amp;rsquo; developments, and their innovative products.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>By setting YZBSTC news we hope our readers both foreign and Chinese could learn more about the latest events and news. Together, we can develop Hainan free trade port zone with great companies that can settle in Yazhou bay science and technology city to build and re-design the future.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Archives</title><link>https://yzbst.city/archives/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yzbst.city/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://yzbst.city/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://yzbst.city/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>